gettingthingsdone.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Getting Things Done®

WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

1\. INTRODUCTION. The David Allen Company (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website (the “Site”).We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, to explain the types of personal information we collect from and about you and how we use, disclose and protect the personal information as well as your ability to control certain uses of it.

2\. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
(a) TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED. We may use cookies or similar technologies to collect information when you visit our Site, use our online services, purchase our online products or interact with our online advertisement. This type of information may include: your type of browser or device, details of the web pages you have viewed, links you clicked on, your IP address, sites clicked on before coming to our Site and any other information you choose to share when using the different social media buttons on our Site. For more information on cookies and how to manage them, please see our Cookie Policy.  
(b) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED IN THE ONLINE STORE. In order for you to purchase products that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes your name, e-mail address, billing address, and financial data, such as your account or credit card number and your name on the credit card.  
(c) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED DIRECTLY FROM YOU. This is personal information you provide us if you communicate with us by filling in application forms, e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, contest entries, or register for our newsletter, any information provided in such communication and/or registration may be collected as Personal Information. This type of Personal Information may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, user name, telephone number, age, date of birth, or gender.  
(d) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM FORUM REGISTRATION. In order for you to create an account we require you to provide us with certain Personal Information. This type of Personal Information may include your e-mail address, user name, and date of birth. For more information about our forum please see our Terms of Use.  
(e) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM GTD CONNECT REGISTRATION. In order for you to receive a free two-week trail membership for GTD Connect we require you to provide us with certain Personal Information. This type of Personal Information may include your e-mail address, name, user name and password. If you use the option to convert to a paid membership for GTD Connect we require you to provide us with additional Personal Information. This type of Personal Information may include Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number and your name on the credit card), your billing address and phone number. For more information about GTD Connect please see our Terms of Use.

3\. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.  
(a) USE OF INFORMATION. We collect your Personal Information to provide you with the required services or information. The following are examples of how we may use the personal data we collect:

  * provide you with services and products that you request from us
  * send you an invoice for our services and products
  * resolve consumer and/or product and services issues
  * anticipate and resolve problems with any services and products supplied to you
  * improve your customer experience on our Site
  * do research and analysis to maintain, protect, develop and improve our services
  * deliver customized content or advertising such as personalized offers for products and services that may be of interest to you
  * communicate regularly with you to inform you about service updates, content, special offers and advertisements that may be of interest to you
  * participate in our online communities, including our social media channel/pages and blogs
  * store your preferences for future interactions and communications from us
  * create external marketing & analytics reports
  * prevent illegal activities, suspected fraud and potential threats to our network
  * analyze the characteristics of our customers at an aggregated level and customer utilization of our products and services in order to understand customer and market needs, to improve our existing products and services, to design new products and services and for business development

(b) SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We share certain categories of Personal Information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share this with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We do not currently share Personal Information with other companies or third parties for any purpose other than our own Company purposes. In the event we do wish to share Personal Information with other companies we ask for your prior explicit consent (opt-in).. We reserve the right to share Personal Information with business partners to assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment of the agreement with you, or data storage and security) related to our business activities and/or operation of the Site. If we do share any such data with business partners, we will require those business partners to agree to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy. The business partners will only use your Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to the Company. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with any third parties, please email us at websupport@davidco.com, but please understand that such a request will likely limit your ability to take advantage of all of the features and services we offer on the Site.  
(c) USER CHOICE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. If you wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our partners, you may select the appropriate “opt-in” option each time we ask for your Personal Information. If you do elect to provide us with Personal Information, we may use that information for any of the purposes identified above, unless you have specifically chosen to “opt-out.”

4\. CONFIDENTIALITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order if we are legally entitled or required to do so; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use.

5\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.  
The collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information is safeguarded by technological and organisational security measures with the objective to protect the Personal Information against loss, misuse and unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. These measures are continually improved in line with technological developments.  
Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers located in the United States that are not accessible by third parties. We transmit sensitive Personal Information, such as financial data, via secured channels.  
We will not retain your personal data for a period longer than necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected, unless we have to keep it for legitimate business, tax, or legal purposes.

6\. YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS.  
You are entitled to know whether we hold Personal Information about you and, if we do, to have a copy of that information. Furthermore, you can request us to correct, update or delete your personal data in our records and/or inform us about any misuse of your personal data. You also have the right to data portability.  
We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date in our online store, forum, and/or GTD Connect. At any time, you may visit your personal profile.  
Through your personal profile you may review and update your Personal Information. Please note that our online store, forum, and GTD Connect are separate databases, and you will need to update your information in each one if you have a profile. In the case of electronic direct marketing, we will provide you with a method to opt out of receiving further marketing materials or with a method to opt in if required by law. If you wish to contact us regarding your Personal Information, or object to our use of your Personal Information, you may do so by e-mailing us at websupport@davidco.com. You can also make a complaint to the relevant privacy authority.

7\. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION. Please notify us promptly at websupport@davidco.com if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without your permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly.

8\. PUBLIC INFORMATION. The Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to Personal Information collected, used and restored in connection with the use of our products, services and Site.  
We may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

9\. CONTACT INFORMATION  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or your privacy, you can contact us at:  
David Allen Company  
201 East Ojai Avenue #788  
Ojai, CA 93024  
USA

customerservice@davidco.com

10\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY. We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. By continuing to access our Site or to make use of our products and services, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

Last Revised: May 23, 2018

David Allen Company Website Privacy Policy
